

Md. Abu Saleh

Personal Info

Mobile: +8801772066066

Email: abu35-1746@diu.edu.bd

Address: 15/1, Sobhanbag Dhaka, Bangladesh-1209

in linkedin.com/hafeezurrahmansaleh

git github.com/hafeeezurrahmansaleh

Skills

Technical Skills

Python

Django

Sqlite and postgresql

••••••

Mobile Application Development Using Java

C# + ASP.NET •••••••

Knowledge on MySQL and Oracle

Software Documents

Javascript ••••••

MS Office

Soft Skills

Communication Skill

Leadership

Problem Solving

Languages

Bengali- Native

English- Reading Writing Speaking Speaking

An independent and self-motivated undergraduate student with a record of academic and extracurricular success. Extensive leadership experience, particularly within a higher education setting. Adept at working across departments, with faculty, administrators, and students. Have a very good communication skills with multiple language proficiency.

Education

2016-2020 BSc. In Software Engineering
 Daffodil International University, Dhaka
 Continuing BSc. in Software Engineering

• **Average CGPA: 3.96** (out of 4)

2013-2015

Higher Secondary Certificate

Amrita Lal Dey College, Barishal

Field of Study: ScienceGraduation year: 2015

2012-2013

Secondary School Certificate

Sagardi Islamia Kamil Madrasah

Field of Study: ScienceGraduation year: 2013

Work History

2019-Present

Volunteer

International Affairs, DIU

 Worked as an International Volunteer in 3 days long 18th Asian University Presidents Forum 2019 and other international events.

2018-Present

Student Volunteer

Students' Affairs, DIU

- Participated in meetings to discuss new fundraising opportunities.
- Worked with organizing team of 17th Foundation Anniversary of DIU.

Projects

☐ Semester Pre-Registration Portal [Fall-2019]

Developed a system by using **Django** with **MySql** backend. Students can complete their pre-registration, teachers and admins can handle all the activities of student advising/registration.

Link: github.com/hafeeezurrahmansaleh/semester_preregistration_system.git

☐ Smart Lab Assistance [Summer-2019]

Developed a Lab Assistance software to manage all the lab activities for both teacher and student by using **Django** framework with **Python3** and **sqlite3** database system.

Project link: github.com/hafeeezurrahmansaleh/Daily-Lab-Assistance.git

☐ CV Maker[Spring-2019]

Created an web based CV/Resume making site by using **PHP** and **MySQL**. Project link: github.com/hafeeezurrahmansaleh/CV-Maker.git

☐ Daily Meal & Expense Tracker [Fall-2018]

Created an online based meal and expense tracking system for student hostels by using **asp.net with C# and SQL Server**.

Project link: github.com/hafeeezurrahmansaleh/Meal-Expense-tracker.git